Guide to the Arthur Liman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Oversize
  - Judicial conference, Circa 1970s (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, 1996-2001; Accession 2003-M-023
  The addition consists of one piece of correspondence, one photograph, and publicity materials, mostly from the Arthur Liman Public Interest Fellowship and Fund.
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1998-2001, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)